[{"question":"What was Martin Luther King, Jr.'s age at death?","answer":39},
{"question":"What is the length of the Nile River, in miles?","answer":4132},
{"question":"How many countries belong to OPEC?","answer":12},
{"question":"How many books are there in the Old Testament?","answer":39},
{"question":"What is the diameter of the moon, in miles?","answer":2158.7678},
{"question":"What is the weight of an empty Boeing 747, in pounds?","answer":390000},
{"question":"In what year was Mozart born?","answer":1756},
{"question":"What is the gestation period of an Asian elephant, in days?","answer":645},
{"question":"What is the air distance from London to Tokyo, in miles?","answer":5959},
{"question":"What is the deepest known point in the ocean, in feet?","answer":35994}]